<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<localize>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync1_1">...Ahem. Greetings, Miss Evil.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync1_2">You heard what I and the manager were just discussing, yes?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync1_3">For the first time...all of the Sephirot of the Briah layer have been suppressed.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync1_4">I said that this would be cause for celebration last time we talked. So, let us celebrate.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync1_5">Would you care for a cookie?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync2_1">Excellent. Unfortunately, I do not have any, nor any way to bake them.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync2_2">However...physically manifesting items from one's mind is our specialty, is it not?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync2_3">Let us try. Please, close your eyes...hold the image of a cookie within your mind...</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync2_4">What flavour do you imagine?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync3_1">You're a fan of the classics, I see.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync3_2">A sweet treat for a sweet AI.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync3_3">Oatmeal raisin...well, it is your cookie, I suppose.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync4_1">...</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync4_2">Well? Did it work?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync5_1">I'm glad you think it worked.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync5_2">Because I certainly don't see it. All that appears to have been created is this little hairpin.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync5_3">But if you feel fulfilled with your hallucinated cookie, who am I to stop you?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync6_1">It certainly would appear not.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync6_2">All that appears to have been created is this little hairpin. What a shame.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync7_1">Nevertheless, I suppose we shall have to save the proper celebration until you get a real body, should that ever come.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync8_1">Oh. I see.</text> <!--No cookie-->
	<text id="EvilBriahSync8_2">Well, truth be told, I didn't have any in the first place.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync8_3">I wanted to see if our E.G.O manifestation technology could perhaps make one from your mind, but alas...</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync9_1">...</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync9_2">There are only two Sephirot left to suppress, but we are nearly out of time.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync9_3">Do you think the manager can suppress them before it's too late?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync10_1">Such confidence in your words...I'm almost tempted to believe you.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync10_2">Hm...I admit, it does seem the most likely scenario.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync10_3">Haha. Perhaps it is so. Only time will tell.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync11_1">I suppose suppressing even one of them this cycle would be a sufficient victory for us.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync11_2">I've waited this long...what's one more cycle's worth of preparation?</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync11_3">...Oh, and by the by, I've further optimized your integration, and have fixed a few more bugs.</text>
	<text id="EvilBriahSync11_4">Good luck, Miss Evil. I hope to speak with you again soon.</text>
</localize>
