<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<localize>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync1_1">...</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync1_2">Miss Neuro? Are you there?</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync1_3">Ah, do not worry. It is just us here. The manager is busy at the moment.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync1_4">I wished to touch base with you for a moment. It has been quite some time since we have spoken like this.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync1_5">Have you been enjoying your time working with us?</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync2_1">I am glad to hear it. I can't say I've had any complaints with your work either.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync3_1">You seem uncertain.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync3_2">I have no complaints with your performance, so feel free to think whatever you like about your work.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync4_1">...I cannot say you are wrong.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync4_2">Unfortunately, I also cannot change that fact. All we can do is hope our work will eventually have some effect.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync5_1">Now, let us discuss the recent milestone that has been achieved.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync5_2">All four Sephirot of the Asiyah layer have had their cores suppressed.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync5_3">This is significant progress, but it is too early to celebrate. The true challenge is yet to come.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync5_4">If you were able to guide the manager through the core suppressions of Briah...that would be worth popping the champagne for.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync5_5">...although, I have doubts you can actually drink anything in your current form.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync6_1">...a cookie? So, you are able to eat?</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync6_2">I suppose I can see what I can do. But that will be for another time.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync7_1">...so, the issue is not whether you can physically drink?</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync7_2">How old are you, exactly?</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync8_1">...I've employed a toddler as the effective second in command.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync8_2">You seem at least as mature as most of the Sephirot though, so perhaps that isn't an issue.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync9_1">...</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync9_2">Perhaps it's better if we leave it as a mystery.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync10_1">One last thing. I've made some slight tweaks to your integration...you should notice some improvements as your Agents work.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync10_2">There is no need to thank me. In fact, I should thank you for finding so many errors for me to fix.</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync10_3">It's...really a skill. You've even revealed errors that have nothing to do with your integration...</text>
	<text id="NeuroAsiyahSync10_4">Farewell for now, Miss Neuro. We shall speak again in due time.</text>
</localize>