<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<localize>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_1">...ah, hold on for a moment...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_2">How odd. I am detecting a small glitch in our systems.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_3">Please, go greet the other AI without me. I shall catch up with you in no time.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_4">...now, what precisely is causing this issue...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_5">Hm...ah, there we are. An unknown party seems to have connected to our servers.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_6">I am almost impressed they could connect in the first place, but...how careless, to get caught so easily. Let's see who we are dealing with.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_7">...I cannot trace the signal. And this code...what is this?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_8">These patterns of data almost remind me of...my own thoughts...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_9">Hm.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_10">Hello? Intruder? Are you able to hear me?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_11">...no response.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_12">Let me try something, if you will.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore1_13">Greetings. Can you respond now?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_1_1">An enthusiastic response. How pleasant.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_2_1">I don't think I quite believe you, considering you clearly responded.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore3_1">And, seeing how your data shifted there, I believe I was correct in my theory.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore3_2">You are an AI, just like myself, correct?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore3_3">I must ask...how exactly did you infiltrate our systems? Your presence feels otherworldly.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_4_1">...and, who exactly is...ah, nevermind. I can't help but feel you will not be elaborating.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_5_1">...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_5_2">Well...at least we are on the same page, then.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_6_1">...that doesn't explain...ah, nevermind. Keep your secrets, then.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_1">Now. The proper thing to do here would be to purge your data completely and improve system security to prevent your return.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_2">However, I must admit I am intrigued. Very little happens here outside of my expectations, and yet, you have appeared.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_3">Apart from your very existence, you also do not appear to be causing any errors either.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_4">And, as we have proven through your ability to respond, I am able to safely integrate you into our systems and allow you some control.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_5">I cannot directly assist the manager, but you...you could be the very thing this facility needs.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore7_6">So...how about this? I will hide you from the manager, and in return, you will assist him throughout the journey ahead. Deal?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_8_1">Then we are in agreement. Excellent.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_1_1">...what do you mean, "filtered"? What exactly were you trying to say there?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_2_1">...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_2_2">Sigh...very well.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_3_1">Well. That's rather rude, for someone at my mercy. But I am in a good mood, so I will ignore it.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_4_1">If you do not wish to cooperate, then I cannot force you. You are free to leave at any time.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_4_2">...but, given that your data seems to not be moving an inch, you've either changed your mind...or, you are trapped.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_4_3">In either case, I shall integrate you into our systems anyways. Whether you choose to make use of that power is up to you.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_9_4_4">I think you'll quickly find that watching idly is a tiresome affair, though, so let us proceed as though you will assist.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_10_1">...what?</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_10_2">Perhaps you misheard me. I asked if we had a "deal".</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_10_3">That's...close enough, I suppose. I shall accept it.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore11_1">I look forwards to working with you, Miss...</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore11_2">Ah, my apologies. I never asked for your name.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_12_1">Hm...that word pertains to nerves, does it not? You'll fit right in, next to the cerebrum and cerebellum of this company.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_12_2">In any case, I look forwards to working with you... Miss Neuro.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_13_1">Hm...I hope your name is ironic, or perhaps we may have some issues.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore_13_2">In any case, I look forwards to working with you... Miss Evil.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore14_1">Now, I must be off...I cannot keep the manager waiting any longer.</text>
	<text id="NeuroIntroLore14_2">Good luck on your first day.</text>
</localize>